Register of the Survey of Race Relations records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Major Documents, 1905-1926 (Boxes 24-32)
  - Interview with Ruby Hirose (Box-folder 27: 159)
    4 pages; Life histories, Competition and land: Agriculture, Race consciousness, Americanization; Japanese; Seattle
  - Interview with Commissioner Weedin, immigration station, Seattle, 1924 April 23 (Box-folder 27: 160)
    3 pages; Population, Other: Illegal entry; Japanese and Chinese; Seattle
  - Interview with C. F. Greiner concerning Mark Ten Suie (Box-folder 27: 161)
    3 pages; Life histories, Intermarriage, Competition and Land: Business; Chinese; Seattle
  - Extract, letter from assistant ethnologist, Honolulu, regarding marriage of Korean to white girl, 1924 June 7 (Box-folder 27: 162)
    1 page; Intermarriage; Korean; Seattle
  - Life history of Tadao Kimura, valedictorian, Seattle High School, 1924 July 31 (Box-folder 27: 163)
    3 pages; Americanization: Second generation and accommodation, Goodwill; Japanese; Seattle
  - "Seattle's Japanese George Washington," by Ruth H. Greiner (Box-folder 27: 164)
    8 pages; Race consciousness, Americanization; Japanese; Seattle
  - "My Contacts with Orientals," by K. Lentz, teacher, Franklin High School (Box-folder 27: 165)
    3 pages; Americanization: Education; Japanese; Seattle
  - "My Experience with Oriental People," by Miss Delano, art teacher, Franklin High School (Box-folder 27: 166)
    1 page; Competition and land: Labor, Americanization; Chinese and Japanese; Seattle
  - Copy of a letter sent to Dr. Suzzello, President, University of Washington, regarding exclusion of Japanese (Box-folder 27: 167)
    1 page; Race consciousness: Public opinion; Japanese; Seattle
  - "Interview with A. V. Williams as Social Document," by C. H. Burnett, 1924 June 26 (Box-folder 27: 168)
    5 pages; Social disorganization: Gambling, Tongs, Americanization: Accommodation, Racial traits; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Interview of Atwood A. Kirby as Social Document," by D. H. Johnson, 1924 August 18 (Box-folder 27: 169)
    6 pages; Social disorganization: Crime, Tongs, Communities; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Interview of Chas. F. Riddell as Social Document," by D. H. Johnson (Box-folder 27: 170)
    7 pages; Social disorganization: Crime, Tongs, Communities; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Life History of Long C. Dong as Social Document," by C. H. Burnett, 1924 July 28 (Box-folder 27: 171)
    6 pages; Life histories, Population: Immigration, Tongs, Race consciousness, Investigations: Legislation; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Life History of Bong Chin as Social Document," by C. H. Burnett, 1924 August 7 (Box-folder 27: 172)
    5 pages; Life histories, Population: Immigration, Race consciousness; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Intermarriage: A Case Study," by K. Lentz (Box-folder 27: 173)
    3 pages; Intermarriage; Japanese; Seattle
  - Interview with Mrs. S. Sasabe, 1924 May 28 (Box-folder 27: 174)
    4 pages; Intermarriage, Race traits, Americanization; Japanese; Seattle
  - Interview with Mrs. Mitsue Miyagawa, Mrs. Tashiro, interpreter, 1924 June 11 (Box-folder 27: 175)
    4 pages; Life histories, Competition and land: Business, Race consciousness, Americanization; Japanese; Seattle
  - Interview with Mrs. Nao Tashiro, 1924 May 28 (Box-folder 27: 176)
    4 pages; Life histories, Goodwill, Disillusion, Americanization, Racial traits; Japanese; Seattle
  - An interracial romance (Box-folder 27: 177)
    2 pages; Intermarriage; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Life History of Andrew Kan as Social Document," by C. H. Burnett, 1924 August 22 (Box-folder 27: 178)
    16 pages; Life histories, Competition and land: Business, Goodwill: Religious activities, Tong, Americanization: Family problems, Population: Immigration, Social Disorganization; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Life History of Kee Low," interviewed by C. H. Burnett, 1924 August 4 (Box-folder 27: 179)
    8 pages; Life histories, Population: Immigration, Race consciousness, Intermarriage, Racial traits; Chinese; Seattle
  - Interview with Mrs. Findley, storekeeper at Eastland, Washington (Box-folder 27: 180)
    2 pages; Racial traits; Japanese; Seattle
  - "Life History of Lum Ming Tak as Social Document," by C. H. Burnett, 1924 August 13 (Box-folder 27: 181)
    7 pages; Life histories, Goodwill: Religious activities, Tongs, Social disorganization: Gambling, Americanization: Family problems, Intermarriage; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Life History of J. S. Look as Social Document," by C. H. Burnett, 1924 August 13 (Box-folder 27: 182)
    7 pages; Life histories, Population: Immigration, Race consciousness, Investigations: Legislation; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Life History of Woo Gen," interviewed by C. H. Burnett, 1924 July 29 (Box-folder 27: 183)
    14 pages; Life histories, Population: Immigration, Goodwill, Race war, Competition and land: Business, Americanization: Second generation, Communities; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Life History of Ying Foy as Social Document,' by C. H. Burnett, 1924 August 11 (Box-folder 27: 184)
    5 pages; Life histories, Americanization: Second generation, Tongs, Racial traits; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Interview of George T. Meyers as Social Document," by C. H. Burnett, 1924 July 27 (Box-folder 27: 185)
    3 pages; Competition and land: Labor, Americanization: Family problems, Marriage?; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Life History of Chin Yen as Social Document," by C. H. Burnett, 1924 August 24 (Box-folder 27: 186)
    10 pages; Life histories, Population: Immigration, Americanization, Racial traits; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Life History of Chin Cheung as Social Document," by C. H. Burnett, 1924 August 21 (Box-folder 27: 187)
    10 pages; Life histories, Americanization: Accommodation, Intermarriage, Competition and land: Business, Tongs, Investigations: Legislation, Chinese; Seattle
  - Interview with a young Chinese boy, graduate of Oregon Agricultural College, by C. H. Burnett, 1924 August 9 (Box-folder 27: 188)
    6 pages; Communities, Tongs, Social disorganization: Vice and crime; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Life history of Charlie Lui as Social Document," by C. H. Burnett, 1924 August 21 (Box-folder 27: 189)
    11 pages; Life histories, Lotteries, Tongs, Population: Immigration; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Interview with Mr. Faris," Deputy Commissioner of Immigration, Seattle, by C. H. Burnett, 1924 August 6 (Box-folder 27: 190)
    12 pages; Population: Immigration; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Life History as Social Document of Law Yow," Seattle, Washington, by C. H. Burnett, 1924 August 12 (Box-folder 27: 191)
    5 pages; Life histories, Competition and land: Labor, Tongs, Americanization: Family problems, Race consciousness; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Interview with Fred H. Lysons, Attorney," by C. H. Burnett, 1924 July 29 (Box-folder 27: 192)
    12 pages; Racial traits, Morality, Intermarriage, Courtship, Competition and land: Labor, Population: Immigration, Tongs, Superstition; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Life History of Albert King as Social Document," by C. H. Burnett, 1924 July 31 (Box-folder 27: 193)
    17 pages; Life histories, Tongs, Population: Immigration, Racial traits; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Life History of Lew Kay as Social Document," by C. H. Burnett, 1924 August 29 (Box-folder 27: 194)
    11 pages; Life histories, Race consciousness, Tongs, Communities; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Life History of Fred Wong as Social Document," by C. H. Burnett, 1924 August 29 (Box-folder 27: 195)
    7 pages; Race consciousness, Americanization: Vocational problems; Chinese; Seattle
  - Interview with Mrs. M. Furuya, 1924 July 3 (Box-folder 27: 196)
    2 pages; Goodwill: Religious activities; Japanese; Seattle
  - Life story of Mrs. T. Sugihara (Box-folder 27: 197)
    4 pages; Racial traits, Americanization: Accommodation, Family problems, and Second generation; Japanese; Seattle
  - "The Orientals in the Lumber Industry in the State of Washington," by Ronald Olson (Box-folder 27: 198)
    23 pages; Competition and land: Labor, Race consciousness; Oriental/ Asiatic; Seattle
  - "Interview with Mr. Mitchell, Druggist, Lake Stevens," by Ronald Olson, regarding Lake Stevens strike, and also interviews with others about it, including with Rucker Bros. Lumber Company (Box-folder 27: 199)
    8 pages; Competition and land: Labor, Race consciousness; Oriental/Asiatic; Seattle
  - General information regarding Ernest Dolge, Incorporated (lumber), by R. L. Olson, 1924 June 26 (Box-folder 27: 200)
    4 pages; Competition and land, Other: Industry, Racial traits; Japanese; Seattle
  - Digital copy of Box 28
  - General information regarding Grays Harbor Commercial Company (lumber), Cosmopolis, Washington, by R. L. Olson, 1924 July 24-26 (Box-folder 28: 201)
    11 pages; Competition and land: Labor, Communities, Race consciousness; Filipino, Japanese, and Hindu; Seattle
  - General information regarding St. Paul and Tacoma Lumber Company, Tacoma, Washington, by R. L. Olson, 1924 June 25-26 and August 14-15 (Box-folder 28: 202)
    13 pages; Competition and land: Labor, Life histories; Japanese; Seattle
  - General information regarding Crown Lumber Company, Mukiltes, Washington, by R. L. Olson, 1924 August 12-13 (Box-folder 28: 203)
    12 pages; Competition and land: Labor, Social disorganization, Communities, Race consciousness; Japanese; Seattle
  - General information regarding Eatonville Lumber Company, Eatonville, Washington, by R. L. Olson (Box-folder 28: 204)
    23 pages; Competition and land: Labor, Social disorganization, Communities, Race consciousness
  - General information regarding Pacific National Lumber Company, National, Washington, by R. L. Olson, 1924 July 16 (Box-folder 28: 205)
    16 pages; Competition and land: Labor, Social disorganization, Communities, Race consciousness; Japanese; Seattle
  - General information regarding Doty Lumber 8 Shingle Company, Doty, Washington, by R. L. Olson, 1924 July 18 (Box-folder 28: 206)
    6 pages; Competition and land, Americanization: Accommodation, Communities: Standards of living, Life histories; Japanese; Seattle
  - General information regarding Carlisle Pennell Lumber Company, Onalaska, Washington, by R. L. Olson (Box-folder 28: 207)
    18 pages; Competition and land, Americanization: Accommodation, Communities: Standards of living; Japanese; Seattle
  - General information regarding Walville Lumber Company, Walville, Washington, by R. L. Olson, 1924 July 20-21 (Box-folder 28: 208)
    22 pages; Competition and land, Life histories, Communities, Race consciousness; Oriental/Asiatic; Seattle
  - General information regarding Bay City Mill Company, Aberdeen, Washington, by R. L. Olson, 1924 July 28 (Box-folder 28: 209)
    3 pages; Competition and land: Labor, Intermarriage, Life histories; Oriental/Asiatic; Seattle
  - General information regarding N 8 M Lumber Company, Rochester, Washington, by R. L. Olson, 1924 July 22 (Box-folder 28: 210)
    7 pages; Competition and land: Labor, Race consciousness, Intermarriage, Life histories; Japanese, Hindu, and Filipino; Seattle
  - "Interview with D. S. Gutabatayao," employed by N 8 M Lumber Company, by R. L. Olson (Box-folder 28: 211)
    1 page; Life histories; Filipino; Seattle
  - "Interview with K. Mori, Japanese Section Foreman," N 8 M Lumber Company, by R. L. Olson (Box-folder 28: 212)
    1 page; Life histories; Japanese; Seattle
  - "Interview with Thomas Masuda," employed by N 8 M Lumber Company, by R. L. Olson (Box-folder 28: 213)
  - "Interview with F. K. Kadomiya, Japanese Cook in the White Boarding House," employed by N 8 M Lumber Company, by R. L. Olson (Box-folder 28: 214)
  - General information regarding Fir Tree Lumber Company, Fir Tree, Washington, by R. L. Olson, 1924 July 24 (Box-folder 28: 215)
    5 pages; Competition and land: Labor, Racial traits, Life histories; Japanese; Seattle
  - Interview with George Murakami, Japanese foreman, Fir Tree Lumber Company (Box-folder 28: 216)
  - "Last Tong War as Told by A. V. Williams: Social Document – Incident," by C. H. Burnett (Box-folder 28: 217)
    1 page; Social disorganization, Tongs; Chinese; Seattle
  - Interview with Henry A. Monroe, attorney, 1924 August 22 (Box-folder 28: 218)
    10 pages; Population: Immigration, Social disorganization, Racial traits; Chinese; Seattle
  - Second interview with Henry A. Monroe, attorney, 1924 August 26 (Box-folder 28: 219)
    6 pages; Social disorganization: Gambling, Tongs, Population: Immigration,; Chinese; Seattle
  - Interview with Mrs. Yamoka, 1924 August 18 (Box-folder 28: 220)
    3 pages; Life histories, Americanization: Accommodation; Hindu; Seattle
  - The Rise of Fong Foo Sec, by James A. Blaisdell (Box-folder 28: 221)
    4 pages; Life histories, Goodwill; Chinese; Southern California). Includes typescript copy
  - "Progeny of Jap-White Union Amaze," extract from San Francisco Examiner, 1922 November 11 (Box-folder 28: 222)
    3 pages; Intermarriage; Japanese; Northern California
  - "Chinese, White Wife Separate," extract from Call, San Francisco, 1921 December 21 (Box-folder 28: 223)
    3 pages; Intermarriage; Chinese; Northern California
  - "Doesn't Want Flappers," extract from Examiner, San Francisco, 1923 March 20 (Box-folder 28: 224)
    2 pages; Intermarriage; Japanese; Northern California
  - Interview with Flora Belle Jan, daughter of proprietor, Yet Far Low Chop Suey restaurant, Fresno, California (Box-folder 28: 225)
    3 pages; Life histories, Americanization: Accommodation; Chinese; Northern California
  - A student in Fresno State College, member of Baptist Mission dormitory and Chinese club, Fresno, California (Box-folder 28: 226)
    4 pages; Life histories, Goodwill, Race consciousness, Americanization: Accommodation; Chinese; Northern California
  - Statement by Reverend J. K. Fukushima, pastor, Japanese Congregational Church, Fresno, California (Box-folder 28: 227)
    3 pages; Goodwill: Religious activities, Americanization, Exclusion; Japanese; Northern California
  - Chinatown Police Squad, Fresno, California (Box-folder 28: 228)
    3 pages; Competition and land: Agriculture,Social disorganization: Gambling, Woman labor; Chinese and Japanese; Northern California
  - Translation from Japanese New World and Japanese-American News, 1922 (Box-folder 28: 229)
    1 page; Competition and land: Agriculture; Japanese; Southern California
  - A Tong situation in Los Angeles (Box-folder 28: 230)
    1 page; Social disorganization, Tongs, Communities; Chinese; Southern California
  - "Anti-Japanese Society Holds Meeting at Clubrooms," Hollywood News, 1924 January 15 (Box-folder 28: 231)
    5 pages; Social disorganization; Japanese; Southern California
  - "Life History of R. Chand (Hindu) of Imperial Valley," by William C. Smith, 1924 June 1 (Box-folder 28: 232)
    8 pages; Life histories, Race consciousness; Hindu; Southern California
  - Life history of a Chinese student (Box-folder 28: 233)
    11 pages; Life histories, Americanization, Race consciousness; Chinese; Southern California
  - "Life History of Sophie Yamanaka," El Centro, California, by William C. Smith, 1924 June 1 (Box-folder 28: 234)
    6 pages; Life histories; Japanese; Southern California
  - "Interview with Mrs. H.," by William C. Smith (Box-folder 28: 235)
    8 pages; Intermarriage, Race consciousness, Americanization; Japanese; Southern California
  - "Adjutant M. Kobayashi on the Second Generation," by William C. Smith (Box-folder 28: 236)
    4 pages; Intermarriage, Americanization; Japanese; Southern California
  - "Interview with Inder Singh (Hindu)," El Centro, California, by William C. Smith, 1924 May 31 (Box-folder 28: 237)
    3 pages; Life histories, Intermarriage, Race consciousness; Hindu; Southern California
  - Case study of a Buddhist temple in Pasadena (Box-folder 28: 238)
    11 pages; Goodwill: Religious activities, Race consciousness; Japanese; Southern California
  - Interview with Esther Wong, native-born Chinese, San Francisco, California, 1924 July 1 (Box-folder 28: 239)
    5 pages; Americanization: Second generation, Race consciousness: Conflicts, Social customs; Chinese; Northern California
  - Letters from Japanese student to Mrs. E. Snell (Box-folder 28: 240)
    16 pages; Americanization: Second generation and Vocational problems; Japanese; Northern California
  - Interview with Mrs. Tame Narita, Mrs. Tashiro interpreter, 1924 June 11 (Box-folder 28: 241)
    3 pages; Life histories, Americanization: Accommodation, Racial traits; Japanese; Seattle
  - "Interview of Pany Lowe, Social Document," by C. H. Burnett, 1924 July 5 (Box-folder 28: 242)
    6 pages; Life histories, Competition and land: Business, Population: Immigration, Race consciousness, Intermarriage; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Interview with Andrew Wu," by C. H. Burnett, 1924 August 25 (Box-folder 28: 243)
    6 pages; Life histories, Race consciousness; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Interview with Mar Sui Haw," by C. H. Burnett, 1924 August 26 (Box-folder 28: 244)
    12 pages; Life histories, Americanization, Intermarriage; Chinese; Seattle
  - Excerpts, report of Fieldbrave, a worker among East Indians on the Pacific Coast, prepared during the year 1924 (Box-folder 28: 245)
    3 pages; Competition and land: Labor, Americanization: Education, Investigations: Legislation; Hindu; Northern California
  - "Life History of Peter S. of Los Angeles," by William C. Smith (Box-folder 28: 246)
    4 pages; Life histories, Americanization, Race consciousness; Japanese; Southern California
  - "Interview with F. T. Nakaya, Japanese Physician," Los Angeles, California, by Catharine Holt, 1924 September 21 and 28 (Box-folder 28: 247)
    13 pages; Life histories, Intermarriage; Japanese; Southern California
  - "Interview with Simioka," Associate Pastor, Japanese M. E. Church, Los Angeles, by William C. Smith, 1924 August 16 (Box-folder 28: 248)
    3 pages; Americanization; Japanese; Southern California
  - "Life History of Hsin J. Yong," by William C. Smith, 1924 November 20 (Box-folder 28: 249)
  - "Interview with Bob Okajaki," by William C. Smith (Box-folder 28: 250)
    4 pages; Americanization, Life histories; Japanese; Southern California
  - Digital copy of Box 29
  - "Life History of Peter," by William C. Smith (Box-folder 29: 251)
    14 pages; Intermarriage, Race consciousness; Japanese and Mexican; Southern California
  - "Oriental Invading Reserves of American," interview with C. C., by William C. Smith (Box-folder 29: 252)
    1 page; Race consciousness; Japanese; Southern California
  - "Oriental Invasion of Reserves of an American," interview with Miss D., by William C. Smith (Box-folder 29: 253)
  - "Interview with Gherkens," by Chloe Holt, 1924 November 8 (Box-folder 29: 254)
    9 pages; Race consciousness; Japanese; Southern California
  - "Interview with Mr. and Mrs. Sessions," Hollywood, by Chloe Holt, 1924 October 20 (Box-folder 29: 255)
    4 pages; Race consciousness; Japanese; Southern California
  - "Interview No. 1 with Mrs. S, Hollywood," by Chloe Holt, 1924 October 27 (Box-folder 29: 256)
  - "Interview No. 2 with Mrs. S, Hollywood," by Chloe Holt, 1924 October 27 (Box-folder 29: 257)
    5 pages; Race consciousness; Japanese; Southern California
  - "Interview with Spaulding, Hollywood," by Chloe Holt, 1924 October 29 (Box-folder 29: 258)
  - Los Angeles County Anti-Asiatic Association on the building of the Japanese churches (Box-folder 29: 259)
    2 pages; Race consciousness: Conflict; Japanese; Southern California
  - Correspondence relating to encroachment of Japanese in Sierra Madre, 1923 September – 1924 January (Box-folder 29: 260)
    17 pages; Race consciousness; Japanese; Southern California
  - Data on Oriental situation in British Columbia (Box-folder 29: 261)
    7 pages; Government, Establishment; Oriental/Asiatic; British Columbia
  - A case of intermarriage, Japanese-American, Los Angeles (Box-folder 29: 262)
    4 pages; Race consciousness, Americanization; Japanese; Southern California
  - "Interview with Mrs. K. Iseri," Los Angeles, and Mrs. Takeyama, by Catharine Holt, 1925 January 3 (Box-folder 29: 263)
    9 pages; Americanization, Race consciousness; Japanese; Southern California
  - Life history of Yamada, California Christian College, Los Angeles (Box-folder 29: 264)
  - "Interview with Florence Kojima," General Secretary, Japanese Division, Y.M.C.A., Los Angeles, by Catharine Holt, 1924 December 11 (Box-folder 29: 265)
  - "Japanese Pupil Elected Student Body President at LeConte Junior High School," Hollywood Daily Citizen, 1922 November 27 (Box-folder 29: 266)
    10 pages; Americanization; Japanese; Southern California
  - "Life History of S--- M--- Y---," by Ethel V. Craig (Box-folder 29: 267)
    8 pages; Life histories, Americanization, Race consciousness; Chinese; Southern California
  - "Life History of H --- I---," Los Angeles, by William C. Smith, 1925 January 25 (Box-folder 29: 268)
    5 pages; Americanization, Race consciousness, Life histories; Chinese; Southern California
  - "Interview with Taro Kanow," by William C. Smith, 1924 December 29 (Box-folder 29: 269)
    3 pages; Americanization, Race consciousness; Japanese; Southern California
  - Life history of J. Lim (Box-folder 29: 270)
    5 pages; Life histories, Americanization, Race consciousness; Korean; Southern California
  - "Life History and Social Document of S. C. Eng," by C. H. Burnett, 1924 August 28 (Box-folder 29: 271)
    4 pages; Life histories, Race consciousness; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Life History and Social Document of David Young," by C. H. Burnett, 1924 August 29 (Box-folder 29: 272)
    11 pages; Life histories, Intermarriage, Communities, Race consciousness; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Hindus in Los Angeles," by Willard A. Schurr (Box-folder 29: 273)
    33 pages; Goodwill, Racial traits, Communities, Race consciousness; Hindu; Southern California
  - Interviews with different people regarding Japanese in Southern California (Box-folder 29: 274)
    152 pages; Racial traits, Race consciousness, Americanization; Japanese and Chinese; Southern California
  - Final report, extracts, from the Office of Labor Agent, State Farm, University of California (Box-folder 29: 275)
    42 pages; Competition and land, Population; Northern California
  - Digital copy of Box 30
  - "My Experiences on a Ranch," by J. P. Weiser (Box-folder 30: 276)
    7 pages; Competition and land; Northern California
  - Report, Commonwealth Club Tenancy Studies, by R. L. Adams, 1922 April-June (Box-folder 30: 277)
    33 pages; Competition and land; Northern California
  - The Anti-Japanese League, Seattle (Box-folder 30: 278)
    16 pages; Competition and land, Communities, Investigations, Life histories; Japanese; Seattle
  - "Japanese Association in America," thesis for the degree of Master of Arts, by Hidesaburo Yokoyama, University of Chicago, 1921 (Box-folder 30: 279)
    54 pages; Communities, Population, Goodwill, Investigations, Race consciousness, Racial traits; Japanese; Northern California
  - Case study of a boy of mixed parentage: Information secured from records of Juvenile Hall and Juvenile Court, Los Angeles, and also from personal contact with the boy (Box-folder 30: 280)
    13 pages; Social disorganization, Life histories, Americanization, Intermarriage; Southern California
  - Jennie's story (Box-folder 30: 281)
    4 pages; Life histories, Heritages, Racial traits; Russian; Southern California
  - Case study of race intermarriage and life history (Box-folder 30: 282)
    11 pages; Life histories, Social disorganization, Communities, Americanization; Japanese; Southern California
  - "The Japanese in British Columbia," by John Nelson (Box-folder 30: 283)
    34 pages; Race consciousness, Competition and land, Communities; Japanese; British Columbia
  - "Message from Japan to America," The Japan Times, 1924 October 1 (Box-folder 30: 284)
    Racial traits; Japanese; Japan